Guide to the Jim Kobs papers, 1954-2015 and undated RL.11721
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Kobs & Brady, 1977-1989; 4
  - Sample Mailings, 1978-1988; 12
    - Binder 9, 1987; 5 folders (Box 15)
      Includes: Allstate, American Express Life, Avis, CBS Video, DHL, Direct Marketing Association, Fidelity Investments, Foster Parents, HBO, Kal Kan, Merabank, Metromail, Quill, Sotheby's, Sports Network, U.S. Mint, Nissan, Newsweek, North American Philips, Peace Corps, Popular Science, Prudential
    - Bell Systems 1 (binder), 1981-1986; 4 folders (Box 15)
      Includes: Card decks, automatic telephone, Bellboy, Biz Pro Multi, call waiting, catalogs, cell phones, Centraflex System, Common Biz Problems, construction, Convenience Calling (16/48 System), credit card, Custom Calling, Dialog intercom, extra phone line
    - Bell Systems 2 (binder), 1979-1986; 4 folders (Box 15)
      Includes: Foofram, Financial Services Multi, gift certificate, In-WATS, Medical Assistant, Motel Dial-Pak, pay phone, Picture Phone, PNB Quarterly, PNB Telescope Series, pushbuttons, RCF Phone Power, residential usage, calendar, speaker phone, survey mailings, Touch-a-matic, Transaction Phone, Yellow Pages
    - Bell Systems 3 (binder), 1979-1981; 3 folders (Box 15)
      Includes: Data Series, Com Key, Horizon
    - Sperry (binder), 1985 (Box 15)
    - U.S. Navy Recruiting Command (binder), 1984-1988; 5 folders (Box 16)
    - Western Publishing (binder), 1981-1987; 4 folders (Box 16)
      Includes: Sesame St. Book Club, Betty Crocker Recipes, The Scribbler, Sesame St. Look Listen & Learn, James Budd Mysteries, Learn About Living, McDonald's & Me Club, Knitting Collection, Simply Beautiful Knitting, Quick and Easy Crocheting, Children's Bible Discovery, Golden Book Video Club, Golden Book Encyclopedia, Green Thumb Plant Cards
    - Xerox 1 (binder), 1980-1981 (Box 16)
    - Xerox 2 (binder), 1980-1982; 4 folders (Box 16)
      Includes: Copiers (550, 2600, 3100, 1020 Marathon), 590 typewriter, catalogs, copiers, Xerox Store
    - Xerox Store (binder), 1980 (Box 16)
- Kobs Gregory Passavant/Kobs Strategic Consulting, 1987-2011 and undated; 5
  - Administrative and General Files, 1988-2007 and undated; 13
    - Allstate case study materials, 1994-1996 (Box 17)
    - Award entries (mostly DMA/Echo), 1990-1999 (Box 17)
    - Award results, 1992-1997 (Box 17)
    - Bayer Bess Vanderwarker, 1989-1994 (Box 17)
    - Billings, 1990-1998 (Box 17)
    - Book promotion, 2nd edition, 1984-1999 (Box 17)
      Kobs, Profitable Direct Marketing
    - Calendars, 1985-2007; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Caples Award, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Case study samples (binder), undated (Box 17)
    - Catalog business model, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Catalog Decision Maker program, 1994-1997 (Box 17)
    - Client letters, 1991-1992 (Box 17)
    - Contacts, 1994-2000 (Box 17)
    - Corporate philosophy, 1993-1994 (Box 17)
    - Credentials, 1989-1992 (Box 17)
    - DMEF (Direct Marketing Educational Foundation) Award, 1988-1990 (Box 17)
    - Employees, 1991-1995 (Box 17)
    - Fee increases, 1989-2000 (Box 17)
    - Forms, 1996-2000 (Box 17)
    - Hall of Fame, 1999 (Box 17)
    - House ads, 1989-2004 (Box 17)
    - IBJ Consulting Group, 1988 (Box 17)
    - IDMN (International Direct Marketing Network), 1995-1996 (Box 17)
    - Internet, 2001-2005 (Box 17)
    - Kestnbaum & Company, 1993-1997 (Box 17)
    - KGP announcement, 1989 (Box 17)
    - KGP products, 1994-1996 (Box 17)
    - KGP startup, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Kobs Strategic Consulting announcements, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Lifetime Value (CADM course), 1998 (Box 17)
    - Loyalty program ideas, undated (Box 17)
    - Mailing list policies, 1996-1999 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1999 (Box 17)
    - Modeling (statistical analysis), 1996 (Box 17)
    - New business planning, 1997 (Box 17)
    - New York Office, 1991-1997 (Box 17)
    - Office space (225 and 205 N. Michigan), 1996 (Box 17)
    - Postal and legal issues, 1990-2006 (Box 17)
    - Promotion plans, 1992-1999 (Box 17)
    - Proposal letters, 1988-2001 (Box 17)
    - Publicity and public relations (news releases), 1989-2001 (Box 17)
    - Sample response report, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Some things we've learned, 1997 (Box 17)
  - Clients, 1987-2011; 14
    - AAM (Asset Allocation & Management), 1990 (Box 18)
    - AARP (American Association of Retired People), 1989-1990 (Box 18)
    - AARP (American Association of Retired People) member file database study, 1991 (Box 18)
    - Ameritech, 1993-1997 (Box 18)
    - Ameritech Cellular, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Ameritech television, 1994 (Box 18)
    - AMRE, 1989-1998 (Box 18)
    - AMRE television, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Archdiocese of Chicago, 2000 (Box 18)
    - AT&T, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - AT&T database search, 1994 (Box 18)
    - AT&T Ideabook, 1989-1990 (Box 18)
    - AT&T mailing schedules, results, 1991-1994 (Box 18)
    - AT&T postcards, 1990-1993 (Box 18)
    - AT&T Soho catalog, 1994 (Box 18)
    - AT&T Sourcebook, 1989 (Box 18)
    - Beer Across America, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Bell Atlantic, 1995-1997 (Box 18)
    - Bennett Lane Winery, 2003-2004 (Box 18)
    - Biltmore Estate, 1992-1994 (Box 18)
    - Blue Cross & Blue Shield, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Blue Cross & Blue Shield direct marketing roundtable, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Bombay, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Bombay--Christmas mail order, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Bombay--Mail order test, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Bombay--Results anaylsis, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Bose, 1991-2001 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Creative, 1993 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Europe, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Mailings, 1991-1997 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Notes, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Report evaluations, 1993 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Space ads, 1991-1997 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Television, 1992 (Box 18)
    - Bose--Wave Radio, 1992-1994 (Box 18)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of Chicago--Board and development, 1995-2004 (Box 18)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of Chicago--Mailings, 1994-1996 (Box 18)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of Chicago--Youth violence report, 1995 (Box 18)
    - Bruml Capital, 1993 (Box 18)
    - CDW (Computer Discount Warehouse), 1997 (Box 18)
    - Coach Leatherware, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - Colorful Images, 1991-2005; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Columbia House, 1993-1996 (Box 18)
    - Concepts Direct, 2001 (Box 18)
    - Conney Safety Products, 1989 (Box 18)
    - Continental Flowers, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - CPK (California Pizza Kitchen), 1995-1996 (Box 18)
    - DDI (Development Dimensions International), 1995 (Box 18)
    - Dictaphone, 1990-1993 (Box 18)
    - Direct Satellite, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Disney, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
    - DMA (Direct Marketing Association), 1989 (Box 19)
    - DMA (Direct Marketing Association) Retention Services, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Domino's Pizza, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
    - Dow Theory Forecasts, 1987-1993; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Dreyfus, 1998-1999 (Box 19)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1999 (Box 19)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica--Mail order, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica--Print, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica--Retail, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Executive Greetings, 1998-1999 (Box 19)
    - Field Museum of Chicago, 2000-2011; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Forbes, 1997 (Box 19)
    - G.L. Tech, 1997 (Box 19)
    - g.Neil Companies, 2000 (Box 19)
    - Gallant Greetings, 2002-2004 (Box 19)
    - Gander Mountain--Christmas, 1991 (Box 19)
    - Gander Mountain--Retail, 1991 (Box 19)
    - Gander Mountain--Spring, 1992 (Box 19)
    - General Electric Consumer Services, 1993-1994 (Box 19)
    - Gevalia--Feasability study, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
    - Guarantee Reserve, 1997 (Box 19)
    - Harlan Checks, 1993-1994 (Box 19)
    - Harris Seeds, 1993-1994 (Box 19)
    - Hewlett-Packard--Loyalty program (Australia), 1995-1996; 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Highlights for Children, 1998-2000 (Box 19)
    - Hooked on Phonics, 1996-1997 (Box 19)
    - HRdirect, 1996-1998 (Box 19)
    - iMaven, 2001 (Box 19)
    - iPilot, 2000-2001 (Box 19)
    - International College of Surgeons, 1998-1999 (Box 19)
    - J.J. Keller, 1997 (Box 19)
    - Jackson-Hirsh, 2000-2001 (Box 19)
    - Juno, 1997-1998 (Box 19)
    - Kraft, 1998 (Box 19)
    - Krames Communications, 1992 (Box 19)
    - Lowenstein Sandler, 1994-2000 (Box 20)
      Expert witnesses in Lucent litigation; includes expert testimony in AT&T antitrust suit 1994
    - MAN Roland, 1996 (Box 20)
    - May Department Stores, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Mayo Clinic--Family health book, 1990-1995 (Box 20)
    - Mayo Clinic--Health letter, 1987-2001 (Box 20)
    - Mayo Clinic--Nutrition letter, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
    - Mayo Clinic--Proceedings, 1991-1993 (Box 20)
    - Mayo Clinic--Scottsdale Clinic, 1991-1992 (Box 20)
    - Mayo Clinic--Television, 1992-2002 (Box 20)
    - MCI, 1990-1996 (Box 20)
    - MCI/American Airlines, 1990-1998; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - MDRT (Million Dollar Roundtable), 1997 (Box 20)
    - Merlite, 1994 (Box 20)
      Expert witness services in Merlite v. Valassis Inserts litigation
    - Microsoft, 1993-1995 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989-2003 (Box 20)
    - Monogram/Montgomery Ward, 1993-1995 (Box 20)
    - Mrs. Field's Cookies, 1994 (Box 20)
    - National Geographic Society, 1990-1992 (Box 20)
    - Nightingale-Conant, 1990-1996 (Box 20)
    - NordicTrack, 1991-1994 (Box 20)
    - NordicTrack--NordicLife, 1993 (Box 20)
    - NordicTrack--NordicSport, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Omaha Steaks, 1984-1992 (Box 20)
    - Panache, 1997-1999 (Box 20)
    - Paragon Direct, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Parlan Video, 1992 (Box 20)
    - Peggy Notebaert Nature Museum, 2001 (Box 20)
    - Pitney Bowes, 1991-2000; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Polk, 1999-2000 (Box 20)
    - Premier Golf Resorts, 1990-1991 (Box 20)
    - Procyon Pharmaceuticals, 1997 (Box 20)
      Expert witness solicitation, Procyon v. Alexis Corporation
    - Quaker Oats, 1989-1993 (Box 20)
    - Quill, 1989-1995; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Reiman Publications, 1992 (Box 20)
    - Rich Products, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Rodale Nature Book Society, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
    - RPS (Retired Persons Services: administrator for AARP Pharmacy Service), 1990-2001; 2 folders (Box 20)
    - Sara Lee (Dim brands, France), 1991-1992 (Box 21)
    - Scholastic Publishing, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Scott-Foresman, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Select Comfort, 1993-1995 (Box 21)
    - SelfCare, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Shaklee, 2001 (Box 21)
    - Shop at Home, 1995-1997 (Box 21)
    - SIE (Select Information Exchange), 2001-2005 (Box 21)
    - Siemens, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
    - Signature Group, 1993-1999 (Box 21)
    - Smithy, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Southwestern Bell, 1991 (Box 21)
    - Specialty Store Services, 2001 (Box 21)
    - St. Paul Federal Bank, 1988-1990 (Box 21)
    - Suave (hair care), 1991-1994 (Box 21)
    - Successories, 1994-1995 (Box 21)
    - Swiss Colony, 1989 (Box 21)
    - Taste of California, 2004-2006 (Box 21)
    - Teaching Company, 1992-1997 (Box 21)
    - Telecordia, 2000 (Box 21)
    - Tinnitus (American Tinnitus Association), 2001-2002 (Box 21)
    - Trump Casino, 1989 (Box 21)
    - TuTTi USA, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Uline, 1990-2006; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Ultimo, 1998 (Box 21)
    - Unimed, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Warner Brothers, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
    - Warshawsky/J.C. Whitney, 1989 (Box 21)
    - Wells Fargo, 1996-1998 (Box 21)
    - Wine Insiders, 2006-2008; 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Wordsquare Publishing, 1999-2000 (Box 21)
    - WTTW, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Sample Mailings, 1989-2003; 15
    - Sample binder 1, 1990-1999; 6 folders (Box 22)
      Folder 1: AAM (Asset Allocation and Management), AARP (American Association of Retired People), Amerin Guaranty, Ameritech; folder 2: American Express, Amre Sears, Archdiocese of Chicago, AT&T; folder 3: AT&T; folder 4: AT&T, Baldwin Cooke; folder 5: Better Homes & Gardens, Biltmore Estate, Blue Cross, Bose; folder 6: Boys and Girls Clubs, CADM (Chicago Association of Direct Marketing, Cardinal Colorprint, CareerTrack, CDW (Computer Discount Warehouse)
    - Sample binder 2, 1991-2003; 5 folders (Box 22)
      Folder 1: Colorful Images, Dartnell, Dependicare, Dictaphone, Direct TV, Disney, DMA (Direct Marketing Association); folder 2: DMEF (Direct Marketing Educational Foundation), Dow Theory Forecasts, Dreyfus; folder 3-5: Encyclopedia Britannica
    - Sample binder 3: The Field Museum (Chicago), 1997-2002; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Sample binder 4, 1989-2000; 4 folders (Box 22)
      Folder 1: Executive Greetings, Forbes, Fort Dearborn/Blue Cross Blue Shield, Foster Gallagher, Gander Mountain, Gatorade, GL Technology; folder 2: G. Neil, Guarantee Reserve, Harris Bank, HR Direct; folder 3: HR Direct, Illinois Bell, ICS (International College of Surgeons, Jackson-Hirsh, J.J. Keller; folder 4: Man Roland
    - Sample binder 5, 1990-1999; 6 folders (Box 23)
      Folder 1: Mayo Clinic, MBW Marketing Group, MCI/Sears, MDRT Center for Productivity; folder 2: Misco, Monogram/Montgomery Wards, Nightingale-Conant; folder 3: Nightingale-Conant; folder 4: Nightingale-Conant, NordicTrack, Omaha Steaks; folder 5-6: Pitney Bowes
    - Sample binder 6, 1990-2000; 5 folders (Box 23)
      Folder 1: Premier Golf Resorts, Quaker Oats (Cycle dog food); folder 2: Quaker (AARP/Kretschmer, Cap'n Crunch), Quill, Reiman Publications; folder 3: Reiman Publications, Scholastic; folder 4: Scott Foresman, Sculpture Group, Select Comfort; folder 5: Siemans, Shop At Home
    - Sample binder 7, 1990-2000; 5 folders (Box 23)
      Folder 1: AARP Member Choice; folder 2: AARP Member Choice, RPS Prescription Savings Program, AARP Pharmacy Service, AARP Health Care Options; folder 3-5: AARP Pharmacy Service/United Healthcare, RPS Prescription Savings Program
    - Sample binder 8, 1989-2000; 3 folders (Box 23)
      Folder 1: Signature Group, Society of the Divine Word; folder 2: Southwestern Bell, St. Paul Federal Bank; folder 3: St. Paul Federal Bank, Stephen Fossler, Suave (shampoo), Systems Compatibility. Teaching Company
    - Sample binder 8, 1989-2000; 3 folders (Box 24)
      Folder 4: Teaching Company, Ultimo, Video Arts; folder 5: Wells Fargo; folder 6: Wells Fargo, World Book, Zethcon, Zurich fund/Kemper
    - Sample binder materials, 1990-2000 (Box 25)
      Includes materials removed from binders 1-8: DMA, Encylopedia Britannica, Executive Greetings, International College of Surgeons, Mayo Clinic, National Exercise for Life Institute, NordicTrack, Parlan Video, Pitney Bowes, AARP Member Choice, Signature Group, Southwestern Bell, Wells Fargo
    - Sample dimensional mailings, 1990-1994 (Box 26)
      Includes: AT&T, CDW (Computer discount Warehouse), Encyclopedia Brittanica, Harris Bank, Kobs Gregory Passavant, Quaker Oats (Cycle dog food),
    - Sample dimensional mailings (Wells Fargo), 1998 (Box 25)
- Writings and Speeches, 1969-2015 and undated; 6
  - Speeches and Articles, 1969-2015 and undated; 16
    - 5th anniversary of Kobs & Brady, 1983 (Box 27)
    - 99 Proven Direct Response Offers, 1979 (Box 27)
    - AAP (Association of American Publishers) Seminar, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Adman's Baseball Diary, 1985 (Box 27)
    - Admarks articles, 2011 (Box 27)
    - Advertising Age--A frog becomes a prince, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Advertising Age--The Power of Direct Marketing, 1988 (Box 27)
    - Advertising Age--What do you mean, they took my name off the door?, 1995 (Box 27)
    - Advertising Age--Wish I'd done that, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Agency President's speech, 1988 (Box 27)
    - Allstate article, 1990 (Box 27)
    - Allstate case history, 1986 (Box 27)
    - AMA (American Marketing Association) copy workshop, 1978 (Box 27)
    - AMA (American Marketing Association)--Direct Marketing Update, 1985 (Box 27)
    - Asian Direct Marketing Symposium keynote, 1998 (Box 27)
    - AT&T lunch, 1984 (Box 27)
      Direct Marketing: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow; AT&T Consumer Products Marketing Roundtable
    - AT&T speech, 1978 (Box 27)
    - Atlanta Direct Marketing Day, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Australia speech 1: Marketing strategies, 1988 (Box 27)
    - Australia speech 2: Creative strategies, 1988 (Box 27)
    - Australia speech 3: Double duty, 1988 (Box 27)
    - Australia talks, 1988 (Box 27)
      For Australian Direct Marketing Association "Mastering Maximarketing" convention
    - Author speech, DMA Conference, 1989 (Box 27)
    - B2B Seminar, 1996-1997 (Box 27)
    - Bankers Life and Casualty--Legal services case study, 1981 (Box 27)
    - Bates international meeting, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Bates Worldwide meeting, 1987 (Box 27)
    - BBV (Bayer Bess Vanderwarker) account staff talk, 1989 (Box 27)
    - Bell System BOC DM/DR Conference, 1980 (Box 27)
      What We've Learned about Effective Bell System DM/DR
    - Billock Panel, 1985 (Box 27)
    - Blue Cross, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 27)
      1989: The Power of Direct Marketing; 1990: Beyond the Basics
    - Bond International (Australia), 1988 (Box 27)
    - Book speech, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Boston--Deat Writers Society, 1993 (Box 27)
    - Boston Direct Marketing Club (Box 27)
    - BPAA (Business/Professional Advertising Association), 1976 (Box 27)
      Two Ways Direct Marketing Pays Off on Bottom Line
    - British Direct Marketing Fair, 1981 (Box 27)
    - Burnett talk--The Power of Direct Marketing, 1989 (Box 27)
    - CADM (Chicago Association of Direct Marketing)--35th anniversary, 1989 (Box 27)
    - CADM--60th anniversary, 2015 (Box 27)
    - CADM--Basic course: The Offer, 1981 (Box 27)
    - CADM--Basic Seminar (binder), 1982; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - CADM--Chief Executives talk, 1981 (Box 27)
    - CADM--Copy workshop, 1973 (Box 27)
    - CADM--Dead Writers Society, 1991 (Box 27)
    - CADM--Direct Marketing Days, 1988 (Box 27)
      Advanced Marketing and Database Concepts
    - CADM--Marketing talk, 1981 (Box 27)
      Intermediate seminar on marketing strategy
    - CADM--Offer speech, 1979 (Box 27)
      Importance of the Offer
    - CADM--Offers, 1980 (Box 27)
      Kobs' 99 Proven Direct Response Offers
    - CADM--Panel, 1989 (Box 27)
      Best Creative Ideas of the 80s (and creative trends for the 90s)
    - CADM--Roosevelt speech, 1974-1976 (Box 27)
      Guest lecture, Roosevelt University, course on direct marketing
    - CADM--Speech, 1986 (Box 27)
    - CADM--Start a Business, 1998 (Box 27)
      The Easy Way to Start a Business, and Some Things I've Learned the Hard Way
    - CADM--Strategies talk, Education Day, 2001 (Box 27)
      Marketing Strategies to Maximize Growth for Your Online or Offline Business
    - Canada speech--Database conference, 1995 (Box 27)
    - Carolinas Direct Marketing Association, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Catalog Age--Idea Exchange, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Catalog Age--Test lab, 1983 (Box 27)
      Testing: The Key to Better Response
    - Catalog speech, 1973 (Box 27)
    - Chicago Direct Marketing Day--Consensual Databases, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Chicago Direct Marketing Day--Electronic Media, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Chicago Direct Marketing Day--Marketing Strategies, 1995, 2004; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Chicago Direct Marketing Day--Mini-institute, 1981 (Box 27)
    - Chicago Direct Marketing Day--Panel, 1978 (Box 27)
    - Chicago Direct Marketing Day--Seminar, 1980, 1982; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Chicago Direct Marketing Day--Speech, 1977, 1987; 2 folders (Box 28)
      1987: Marketing Strategies for Maximum Growth
    - Cincinnati speech--Ohio Valley Direct Marketing Day, 1979 (Box 28)
    - Cincinnati speech--Professional Direct Marketing Seminar, 1978 (Box 28)
    - Cleveland Advertising Club, 1979 (Box 28)
    - Cleveland--Northeast Ohio Direct Mail and Marketing Association (NODMMA), 1986 (Box 28)
    - Collegiate Institute, 1973-1985; 4 folders (Box 28)
      1973: Direct Mail Today; 1983: How to Reduce Selling Costs and Increase Profits with Industrial Direct Marketing
    - CORD (Council of Retired Directors) induction, 2012 (Box 28)
    - Crain seminars, 1976-1978; 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Crain seminars--Ad Age High Intensity (binder), 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Creative seminar (binder), 1983 (Box 28)
    - Creativity Then and Now, 1973-1974, 1984; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Dayton Ad Club, 1982 (Box 28)
    - DC Talk--Dead Writers Society, 1995 (Box 28)
    - DeLay article--Integrated Marketing Communications, 1992 (Box 28)
    - DePaul guest lecture, 1996 (Box 28)
    - Detroit Direct Marketing Day--Agency Executive Speech, 1988 (Box 28)
    - Detroit Direct Marketing Day--The Future Begins Yesterday, 1981 (Box 28)
    - DHL sales meeting, 1983 (Box 28)
    - Direct marketing book chapter, 1984 (Box 28)
    - Direct Marketing Careers (Anne Bayse)--Preface, 1992 (Box 28)
    - Direct Marketing Day--Copy speech, 1973 (Box 28)
    - Direct Marketing Magazine--Marketing Strategies article, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Direct Response Marketing to Schools Newsletter--Interview on catalog promotions, 1982 (Box 28)
    - DM in AM (Direct Marketing Club of New York, Sunrise Seminars), 1983 (Box 28)
    - DMA (Direct Marketing Association)--Basics 1: Creative, 1989 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Basics 2: Media, 1989 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Basics 3: Offers and testing, 1989 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Book (slides, video), 1991 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Catalog/space talk, 1990; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - DMA--Consumerism, 1986 (Box 28)
      Ten Trends in Direct Response Advertising
    - DMA--Fall book talk, 1991 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Fall marketing strategies talk, 1988 (Box 28)
    - DMA--French Forum, 1986, 1988; 2 folders (Box 28)
      DMA International Strategic Forum on Direct Marketing
    - DMA--Industrial Managers Institute, 1978-1979 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Marketing Roundtable, 1991 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Professors Institute, 1984 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Spring conference panel, 1983-1989; 3 folders (Box 28)
      1983: Advertising in a recession; 1986: 25 Mistakes You Don't Have to Make and 25 Winners You Might Want to Copy; 1989: Creative Revitalization
    - DMA--Spring direct marketing update, 1984 (Box 28)
    - DMA--Spring offer/basics, 1989 (Box 28)
    - DMAA (Direct Mail Advertising Association)--Panel, 1972 (Box 28)
    - DMEF--Educators' Conference, 1991 (Box 28)
    - DMEF--Graduate seminar, 1995 (Box 28)
    - DMEF--Graduate seminar, 1996 (Box 29)
    - DMEF--Journal article, 1990 (Box 29)
      Advertising Edcuation: Then and Now
    - DMEF--Journal article, 1996 (Box 29)
      Consensual Databases
    - DMEF--Professors' Institute, 1994, 2001; 2 folders (Box 29)
      1994: What Your Students Need to Know About Direct Marketing Creative; 2001: The Internet--Method, Market or Medium?
    - DMIC (Direct Marketing Insurance Council)--Seminar, 1992 (Box 29)
    - DMIX (Direct Marketing Idea Exchange), 1987 (Box 29)
      Marketing Strategies for Maximum Growth
    - DMMA--10 Basics, 1980 (Box 29)
    - DMMA/AT&T speech, 1979 (Box 29)
      10 Steps to Long-Range Success in Direct Marketing
    - DMMA--Atlanta panel, 1976 (Box 29)
    - DMMA--Business/Industrial Council, 1982 (Box 29)
    - DMMA--New technology, 1982 (Box 29)
    - DMMA--Washington panel, 1978 (Box 29)
    - Fall talk, educators conference, 1989 (Box 29)
      Dichotomy of Direct Marketing
    - Fidelity Investments seminar, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Field Museum of Chicago/CADM talk, 2000 (Box 29)
      Direct from the Heart program; The Field Museum Virtually Doubles Membership
    - Florida speech, 1981 (Box 29)
      The Future Begins Yesterday, client case studies
    - Focus interview (New Zealand), 1997 (Box 29)
    - Folio catalog seminars, 1983 (Box 29)
      Moderator, The Great Catalog Idea Exchange panel
    - French forum, 1987 (Box 29)
      DMA Strategic Forum; Case Study of P&K Electronics
    - General Electric private seminar, 1979 (Box 29)
    - HBO case for Stone book, 1987 (Box 29)
      Bob Stone's Successful Direct Marketing Methods, 4th edition
    - Helene Curtis sales meeting, 1982 (Box 29)